- 一直想吐口水 - 好了，好了
that I could just spit! Okay, okay.
就吐在这块地板上
Right here, on this floor!
好啦，好啦，你红脸唱的真好
Okay, okay. Nice Good Cop.
戴夫，我发誓，我们没有 电视上说的那么疯狂
Dave, I swear, it wasn't as crazy as it looked on TV.
是吗？
Oh, really?
我来读几条
Well, let me just pull up some of
喜多昨晚发的微博 给你们听听
Theodore's tweets from last night.
“今晚只能用一个词来形容
"Only one word to describe this night,
疯狂，疯狂，疯狂，疯狂”
"Crazy, crazy, crazy, crazy."
还有，想感受疯狂
Or, "If you wanna get crazy,
就来新奥尔良 这儿最疯狂“
"go to New Orleans. It's the craziest."
还有，新奥尔良爵士乐游行中
Or, "In a New Orleans Jazz Parade,
太疯狂了
"so crazy."
我们真的很抱歉，戴夫
We're really sorry, Dave.
这一次道歉不管用了，伙计们
Sorry's not gonna cut it this time, guys.
换做平时，我们立刻就回家
If it were up to me, we'd be going home,
但是我必须赶回迈阿密
but I gotta get back to Miami.
笑你个头笑 到了迈阿密后禁止外出
Do not smile. You guys are grounded in Miami